Finding Aid for the Van Bogert Papers PASC.0153
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Television Projects
  - You Are There
    - Great Diamond Fraud (The) (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Production materials: script, call sheets, breakdown, bit and cast list, extras cost schedule, production reports.
    - Mr. Christian seizes the Bounty (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - One Man Horse (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Cast and staff list.
    - Salem Witch Trials (Box 15, Folder 15)
      Written by Milton Geiger. 7/30/56.
    - Salem Witch Trials (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Production report.